Darshankumar Joshi

Ahmedabad, Gujarat | 8849790993 joshidarshan756@gmail.com DOB:-07-09-1998

Summary

Reults-driven and dedicated sales coordinator who excels at developing and implementing new sales strategies ,conducting sales reports and analysis ,and preparing contracts. Certified Sales manager with an extensive experience in fast-paced business environments. Offers great communication/leadership skills,excellent time management skills ,and important ability to remain calm under pressure .

Experience

Medicare hygiene limited | Gujarat, Ahmedabad

Sales Coordinator | 02/2023 - Present

- -Generate Preform Invoice and share it with respective Sales person to check and Handle the processing of all orders with accuracy and timeliness.
- -Inform clients of unforeseen delays or problems.
- -Timely follow up for the payment and inform to the Sales team for updating collection status.
- -Prepare Quotation as per requirement of Sales team and Management Team.
- -Attend Daily call and handle query from Sales and Marketing team
- -Coordinate with Dispatch department and Account Department for Customer queries.
- -Prepare Target Achievement Sheet (Sales Data) and share it with Sales director on 10th, 20th and 30th of every month
- -Deposit received PDC cheque as per schedule.
- -Share received Invoice with respective Sales person along with LR (Transport copy)
- -Process customer's product related complaint as per given SOP (Provided by Quality Department)
- -Prepare Product wise Sales Report and share it with Sales team on 10th, 20th and 30th of every month.
- -Check Sales team Expense Report and prepare summary sheet.(TA-DA).
- -Provide Sales team Expenses Summary Sheet to management and ask Accounts team to disburse that amount after confirmation of management.
- -Coordinate with Production department for Sample requirement of sales team.
- -Take follow up for Tour Plan Report of Sales team, if not received by 27th(TP)
- -Attend Daily/weekly meetings and trainings.
- -Handling all logistic queries.
- -Mentioning marketing staff salary sheet.
- -Handling 100+ Filed team members.

Paytm Money Pvt Ltd | Gujarat, Ahmedabad

Operation Executive | 01/2022 - 02/2023

- -Handling merchant channel team, making daily MIS reports of sales team and Submitted to ZSM,RSM and HO.
- -Verified customer document given by field team and online and generated customer id also taken sign of customer on agreement.

Home Credit India Finance Private Limited | Gujarat, Ahmedabad

Sr. Operator | 04/2019 - 12/2021

- -Department :Risk Management
- -Collection of EMI consumer duration, personal loans, sales personal loan and record of all data in excel sheet.

Jubilant FoodWorks Pvt Led | Gujarat, Ahmedabad

Guest delight associate-Silver | 07/2018 - 04/2019

- -Attending walking customer and food making
- -Handel inventory to place order of materials.

Skills

Leadership Experience, Problem Resolution, Time Management, Computer Skills, Microsoft word, Microsoft excel, Documentation review, Communication skills

Education

C.U. Shah Commerce College | Ahmedabad, Gujarat Bachelor of commerce | 03/2019

CGPA:-5.40

Shri Rj Patel Shriji Vidyalay | Ahmedabad, Gujarat HSC | 04/2016

Percentage:-81.14

Shri Ambika Vidyalay | Ahmedabad, Gujarat

SSC | 04/2014 Percentage:-54.18

Languages

English, Hindi, Gujarati

Achievements & Awards

Certificate of appreciation for contribution & dedicated services for achieving 1,00,000 Accounts (IR)for the month of May'22 in Paytm Money.

Thanks Regarding
Darshan Joshi

Mobile:-8849790993